A totally SPACED adventure! ...You have to be there to see it.
The Ice Pirates is a science fiction, action,
adventure film directed by Stewart Raffill.
In the not too distant future, where by far the most
precious commodity in the galaxy is water.
The last surviving water planet was somehow removed to the unreachable
centre of the galaxy at the end of the galactic trade wars.
The galaxy is ruled by an evil emperor presiding over a trade oligarchy that
controls all mining and sale of ice from asteroids and comets.
Jason, played by Robert Urich.
Princess Karina, played by Mary Crosby.
Roscoe, played by Michael D. Roberts.
Maida, played by Anjelica Huston.
Killjoy, played by John Matuszak.
Zeno, played by Ron Perlman.
The Ice Pirates is a 1984 American comic science fiction film directed by Stewart
Raffill, who co-wrote the screenplay with Krull writer Stanford Sherman.
The film stars Robert Urich, Mary Crosby and Michael D.
Roberts; other notable featured actors are Anjelica Huston, Ron Perlman, Bruce
Vilanch, John Carradine and former football player John Matuszak.
The film explores themes of rebel, space war, water shortage, space western.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.